- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Samuel.
I have to ask you some questions.
You haven't been at this
school for long, right?
RECONSTRUCTION OF:
SAN ESTEBAN HIGH SCHOOL
No, almost four months. I
used to attend San Esteban.
San Esteban, the school that collapsed?
Calm down. It's going to be alright.
Another woman's after your husband.
Have you noticed anything off lately?
What are you doing?
It's hers, I was just holding it
for her. This kid, I'm telling you.
To win over the locals,
the construction company decided
to fund three scholarships...
to study here at Las Encinas.
I was one of the lucky ones.
Samu!
- What's up, man?
- How are you?
Hello, beautiful. Shit, sorry.
You're not gonna sacrifice yourself
because of what I said, right?
Do you know each other?
He's a buddy of my brother.
This is fucking paradise, man.
Can't you smell it? Those chicks
pee cologne, dude. I'm telling you.
Let's take a walk around, okay?
Look at that. They stare
as if we were Martians.
You get used to it.
Come, a photo, right? Let's
take a selfie, or something.
Let's take a look around.
You can't use your cell phone here.
If they catch you, they'll
take it, and keep it for a week.
That's against the constitution.
- You've read the constitution?
- No. I'm waiting for the movie.
- It's in the handbook.
- Have you read the handbook?
When your name is Nadia Shana,
you better know what
can get you expelled.
Just in case.
Whoo! The swimming pool
is bigger than the school!
You liked to swim, didn't you?
You were in the same class.
Samuel.
You'd be saving us a
lot of time and work
if you answered a simple question.
Why did you have blood on you?
I've done nothing. I
want a lawyer, please.
What else is forbidden?
Drinking, smoking on
the grounds, doing drugs.
- They don't allow anything cool?
- Depends on what you think is cool.
- Olé.
- Hey!
Whoo-hoo!
- What the fuck, man?
- Sorry!
Don't cry!
This is your classroom.
Wait for your teacher, and after
class I'll assign you lockers.
- Welcome!
- Cool.
- Are you the new students?
- Yes.
Good luck, then. You're gonna need it.
What's up, guys! I'm Christian.
Look at this one.
Hi there.
Hello.
- Not there!
- Is it taken?
- By an invisible friend.
- Oh! Enjoy his company.
Good morning, class! How's
everybody doing today?
Please, sit down.
Okay.
So, as we all know, we have
three new students with us today.
Let's meet them.
- Damn. Wasn't this a tutorial class?
- In English. It's a bilingual school.
You knew that, right?
Christian Varela.
Yes.
Do you want to introduce
yourself to the class?
What's he saying?
- Introduce yourself.
- Ah! Yes.
Um... Hello. Um...
Goodbye?
OK... Great.
Thank you, mister teacher.
- "Mister teacher."
- Nadia Shana.
Hello, I'm Nadia. I'm 16.
My family is from Palestine.
But I was born here in Spain.
And when I finish my studies,
I'd like to be professional
diplomat in the United Nations.
Wow! Impressive.
You know, every year we
choose our best student, and...
the trophy is rather ugly,
but it allows you to study
the following year at...
Who can tell me where?
Carla.
At a school in Florida.
Which gives you access to
an Ivy League University.
- And how can you win it?
- By standing out in all activities.
Curricular and extracurricular. The
more extracurricular, the better.
Photography, chess,
Chinese, check out the list.
If I were you, I'd watch out for
this one. She'll give you no quarter.
Ridiculous.
Wasn't this a secular school?
Samuel García.
Hi. My name is Samuel...
and I feel like anything I
say will be used against me,
- so I'll better remain quiet.
- How darling!
Don't be afraid. At this
school we teach values.
Manners and respect are paramount.
The leaders of tomorrow
are at this school.
I know. That's what I fear.
What did the waiter say?
He's talking to us.
- Guys.
- Sorry.
Alright. My name's Samuel, and I
am, as your classmate said, a waiter.
Strange as it may seem to you,
sometimes waiters get
a seat at the table.
But you don't need to worry, I'm
not here to take anybody's place.
You are still the leaders of tomorrow.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
So, why don't we continue with
where we left it yesterday?
Of all the people there, you
had to mess with my brother.
That was your brother?
And people say we, rich
people, don't suffer.
I see.
- My condolences.
- Thank you.
Shall we?
Hey... in case nobody's told you,
it's cool having you in class.
Thanks.
Hello.
Where are you going?
We'll walk with you.
- Stop being such an asshole.
- Watch that mouth.
We're only trying to be friendly.
What's the matter, waiter?
Do you like my sister?
- She's a fan of lost causes...
- Guzmán, go to hell.
Seriously, leave him alone.
Let us have him for a while.
We want to get to know him.
Or are you afraid of us?
- He is afraid of us!
- He is, yeah.
Waiter... don't lay a hand on my sister.
Imagine you have a restraining order.
Guzmán... take this.
Nadia.
Can you come with me for a
moment? The principal wants a word.
No one had mentioned the scarf.
Why now?
Per our rules, no supplementary
vestures are allowed.
My hijab is not supplementary.
Besides, everybody
has things around here.
Expensive bags, gold watches.
Those are ornamental,
they don't mean anything.
They do. They mean many things.
They mean "I have more money than you,
more style than you.
I'm better than you."
- Nadia, we understand you, really, but...
- Look, if you understood...
you wouldn't ask me to give
up my culture or my religion.
Nadia, think about it.
It's up to you.
But if you wear it tomorrow...
we'll have no option but to expel you.
Who do you think calls the shots here?
Shouldn't you be worrying
about other things now?
About the fact that you speak
no English, for instance.
Come on, it's not "nothing",
it's "a little but."
I got it all under control. You
lend me your notes "in English"...
and I translate them online
to know what it's all about.
I'm not going to give you my
notes. And you shouldn't be here.
You're taking a spot
somebody else actually needs.
Wait, do you think I
am here to study? No.
I'm here to meet the
people who rule the roost.
They are not those with the best grades,
but those who make the best friends.
Watch.
- What time's the party?
- What party?
Anybody say party? Hi, I'm Christian.
Yes. Hello! Do you speak Spanish?
I was talking to my friends.
Oh, sorry. By the way,
are you on Instagram?
I can give you mine, if you want.
Yes, please!
It's "pekechristian007,"
the first one is a "K."
Pekechristian.
Pekechristian. Oh, no!
I've fucking had it with these people.
I don't understand how they
got into this school. I don't.
Wow, this video! Look at this.
Do not touch me!
Lu, don't be mean.
- Pay no attention to my friend.
- So, what about this party?
My sister's coming out party is
private, like our conversation.
Who do I need to talk to
about getting an invite?
You've never partied with me. You
had a roof collapse on you, right?
Maybe the blow impaired
your ability to take a hint.
Shall I say it in
English, so you get it?
Goodbye.
- And if I don't feel like it?
- Look...
As you're slow-witted, you
don't get how things work here.
But your friend there
is starting to get it.
Come, let's go, Guzmán.
Cool video.
Christian, it can happen
to anyone, going too far.
It's the end of the school year party...
There's alcohol.
I don't know, maybe a
fight gets out of control.
What do I have to do with it?
I'm not like that.
Can you interrogate me if
my parents are not present?
These are just questions.
But if you don't want to cooperate,
we can take you to the station.
With your parents, and a lawyer.
How did you get that injury?
I hit myself on a door.
Why do I get the feeling
you are lying to me?
The change may end up
not being all that bad.
How is your new school?
Imagine, I'm a Muslim,
I don't play soccer,
and I was caught reading
a book in the hallway.
There'll be wanted signs
with my face tomorrow.
The reward will be a reggaeton concert.
I'm a dead man, then.
Shit, man, I wish some
rubble had fallen on me
when the school collapsed.
Christian got 14 stitches.
Yeah, and a scholarship
to Las Encinas, dickhead.
With any luck, the same will
happen to you at your new school.
- No such luck, I'm afraid.
- Roofs do collapse.
You're the worst!
Hi.
Look at him.
He looks like a minister.
Little brother!
Goodness me!
- Doing well in fancy-land?
- Yes.
I'm ready to fight
anybody who bothers you.
What are you doing here?
- What, you're not happy to see me?
- Yes! But have they let you out?
No, I'm still there. What do you
think? Come, let's have a beer.
Here you go.
Wow! This is nice, right?
The three of us together again.
- The family goes out tonight.
- I can't tonight.
- You can.
- I work tonight, Nano.
Call in sick, and that's it.
What if they find out I'm lying?
It's the only job we
have since you left.
Is this how it's gonna be?
Samu, I didn't leave.
They made me leave.
- How was your first day?
- Very good.
OPEN
CLOSED
How about this one?
Do you like it?
Mom...
You showed me that one yesterday.
The answer remains the same.
You don't like anything, Marina.
Is it that hard to be
a bit more enthusiastic?
Mom and Dad are doing
all of this for you.
For me?
- But nobody's asked them.
- Sweetheart...
We want to celebrate
that you are a woman,
and you're coming out into society.
Presenting me as a virginal young
lady looking for a boyfriend.
Marina, please.
What?
Are we never going to talk about it?
How about the new students?
A moron, a fundamentalist,
and one with raised fist.
- As a joke, they'd be priceless.
- Hey...
Why don't you ask one
of them to the party?
Are you serious?
Why not?
Have you lost your mind?
Hello. No, I told you
not to worry. Okay?
I think it's a great idea.
Besides, it's my party, right?
Son of a bitch!
Cool.
Hey! Have you seen my
uniform? No? Nothing?
You haven't seen my clothes?
What's up, handsome?
Hello, beautiful. You haven't
seen my clothes, really?
No? Come on! There we are!
Alright, then. Fuck you all.
Enjoy the view! This too, come on.
Wouldn't you like to have this ass.
Hey, would you like to come to a
party at my place tomorrow evening?
Why would you invite me to a party?
Because I need somebody else
to enjoy it as little as me.
Besides, wouldn't you like
to see my brother's face?
Okay.
Your hair looks nice today.
Did you have any problems
with the other students?
No. Not with anybody.
How was your relationship with
the students at the school?
Did you get along? Were you friends?
You're Ander, right?
I've seen all your trophies,
man. I'm crazy about tennis.
Come on, guys! To your next class!
Anybody left in the locker room?
What are you doing?
- Anything wrong?
- No, why?
OK, then. Off to class.
Thanks a lot, man. You're alright.
No, I'm not. I just saved your ass.
You could pay me back.
Guzmán!
- What?
- We've been seen, damn it!
- What is it?
- Shit!
- We've been seen.
Don't worry, he'll be here.
I talked to him ten minutes ago.
Besides, nobody will see
you here, man. Don't worry.
- But can he be trusted, or not?
- Of course!
What's he gonna do? Go on TV to
say a rich boy is buying joints?
Come on! That wouldn't be news.
I just don't want
them to know at school.
Who's going to find out? I won't
tell anyone, don't worry, man.
Besides, I don't even have
any friends in there. Or do I?
Yeah! Good man!
By the way, man, I wanted
to ask you something.
- Shoot.
- Why do you all mess with us so much?
Something happened with
a scholarship student.
The son of one of the cooks.
And they halted
scholarships for a full year.
It was a huge mess.
Until you arrived.
Hey!
What's up, man?
- How are you?
- Hi.
I'll introduce you, Mr. X, Mr.
Dealer. Sorry, no real names.
Thank you, much obliged.
Have you seen how well-mannered?
You can't complain, I
bring you quality clients.
Don't you forget.
By the way, you and I
will talk. You owe me one!
Here we go, now we are all set.
- Hey, my man!
- So good to see you!
Twelve, thirteen, fourteen...
Hang in there! Fifteen,
sixteen, that's it!
So, they make a school
collapse, and get away with it.
Can't wrap my fucking head around that!
- When will the others be released?
- What do I know, man?
That's how the world works.
Some of us in jail for some small shit,
and the real crooks out on the street.
It figures.
I almost didn't live to tell
it. I got a huge cut in my head.
But, that got me a
ticket to fancy-land.
It's no joke, Christian, what
if there had been casualties?
This is not okay. This
country is a fucking joke.
Let's give your brother
a drink, we're losing him!
- There are none left.
- None?
I can solve that in a
second. Be right back.
Man, save, and you can buy it.
A little stuck on that topic, isn't he?
I mean, I don't know, Nano is
like a brother to me, you know.
And... my brother's brother
is also my brother, right?
You want my notes from class?
WELCOME. SHALL WE CREATE YOUR PROFILE?
A GUY
Look at him! Like a baby.
Catch!
I have a romantic idea worthy of
a movie. Jaime, I'm borrowing it.
Nano, can you tell me where we're going?
To visit our friend the
constructor, so he remembers us.
- Get off. Get off!
- What?
Keep watch.
No! What are you doing?
Don't even think about it!
Yes! Let's enjoy it, Samu.
Nano!
You just got out of jail, and this
is the dumbest shit you could do!
Nano, someone's coming! Nano!
- What?
- Someone's coming, let's go!
Motherfucker...
THI
Come on!
Just one more thing, Nadia.
Help us, and then you can go.
What can you tell me about this trophy?
Why?
We think it's the murder weapon.
What?
We've been told you wanted
to win it more than anything.
Just me?
It's her word against ours.
You want to risk them believing her?
- This is all your fault.
- Mine?
Yes, you and your silly obsession
with doing it in public places.
Sure.
As if you didn't like it.
Hello.
Sorry about yesterday.
We thought we were alone.
I wish.
Look, I know we started off on the
wrong foot. I'd like to fix that.
Why don't you come tonight to
my sister's coming out party?
We can get to know each other.
Thanks, but no.
Have a nice day.
Boo!
I love her!
Who? Carla? Her mother
is a Spanish grandee.
Do you know the Marquesado
de Caleruega wines?
- No.
- That's her mommy, the marchioness.
Well, and that guy, Polo, is her
boyfriend, since they were 12.
That one? For real?
No, come on, she deserves much
better. You're fucking kidding me!
If I were you, I'd watch
out for the girls here.
Yeah. I'll be watching this one.
Nadia.
How are you?
Listen, I'd like you
to come to my party.
Thank you, but it isn't my scene.
You can come in your scarf, or
without it. Come as you want, okay?
It's called a hijab.
Not a scarf.
Hijab.
- And nobody forces me to wear it.
- Lucky you!
I do feel like I'm being forced to
have this ridiculous coming out party.
I don't know. Give us a chance.
We're not all like my brother.
It starts at eight.
Samuel has the address.
- Fuck, man, this doesn't pull well.
- Don't laugh at the newbie, okay?
I'm not laughing, for a first joint,
made with a tutorial, it's not bad.
By the way, why the fuck don't
you wanna go to the party?
Still obsessing about the
party, give me a break!
I'm not obsessing,
you may be used to all of
this stuff and this luxury,
but I'm not, this is all new
to me. I'm excited about it.
What do you think? That I
live like the rest of them?
- You don't?
- Not even close.
Then what the fuck are
you doing at that school?
Kid, I'm the principal's son.
Son of a bitch! You
are fucking plugged in!
Anyway...
- You want to go, right?
- Of course.
- Are you positive?
- Completely, yes.
- Do you have anything decent to wear?
- Of course I do, man!
- What are you doing here?
- Nadia wants to go to the party.
And my father says if there's no
alcohol, and there's parents there...
- Say yes, I want to go home.
- Yeah, man, don't worry.
Shit.
This is a serious party.
THI
What's up, Samu?
- Hi.
- You didn't expect to see me here, huh?
Let's go in!
Here you have it, a coming out
party in all its ridiculousness!
What is it for? In other times,
to find a husband quickly.
Nowadays it's more
to widen your network.
Although the husband
thing is not ruled out.
You're so much fun when you drink.
Wow, you rich people
know how to throw a party!
Are you color blind?
Or did you not turn on the
light when you got dressed?
Lu, don't be mean. Handsome guys
look good whatever they wear.
We've already said hi. Are you staying?
I don't know. Do you want me to stay?
- If you say yes, I'll stay forever.
- Well, well, let's start with a drink.
Please.
Ah, move aside.
Can you explain to me why
you've brought the influencer?
- You've brought the girl, right?
- It's my home, Ander.
I don't know, because
he really wanted to come.
Nothing's going to happen.
This whole crusade of yours
against them is ridiculous.
Look...
I forgive you, because
you're really drunk.
But I wouldn't have betrayed
you like that. Never!
What betrayal, Guzmán?
What betrayal?
Fucking champagne! Where's the beer?
You've come.
Dad.
Pleased to meet you.
The balls on you, kid, showing up here!
Don't you know we have security cameras?
Shall we talk later?
Only alcohol can make
this tolerable. Here.
Thanks. I don't drink.
It's going to be a hard night, then.
- I'm leaving soon.
- Of course.
Why give us a chance
when you have already sentenced
and judged us all, right?
Here's everything you
hate about the West.
All the sinful decadence.
I thought I was the one judging.
But I can see you have decided
what I think and what I don't.
With a scarf on your head, you
can't possibly think much, dear.
Is this about me not
accepting the champagne?
Or your congenital racism?
Forgive me. Oh, no, forgive me.
Sorry, I came here in peace, I swear.
I'm sure you and I have
something in common.
Don't worry. I've come
to Las Encinas to study.
I'm not interested in
anything beyond that.
Let me give you some advice, dear.
You can do it all.
Look at me.
I date, I have fun, a lot.
And I'm top of the class.
Or you were. Right?
So? What do you think of my party?
Wouldn't you love to set us all on fire?
OK. I'll order a glass
of water, just in case.
Samuel...
Sorry I didn't tell you my
father's construction company...
- was the one from your school.
- Right. It would have been good to know.
I'm not like him.
And to be honest, I think
I don't even like him.
But he's done all of this for you.
Yeah, he's very good at solving
problems throwing money at them.
Wanna dance?
- What?
- Why are you like this, Lu?
Don't you see? It's not
about the skirt, I don't care.
It's about that Taliban
girl. That little hypocrite.
Wearing a scarf on your head
makes you superior to us?
- Please, how ridiculous!
- I don't want her here either.
But we have to do something,
so she won't tell on us.
I have an idea.
Let's hear it.
I propose a game. Why
don't you seduce her?
Then everybody finds
out... and that's that.
You want me to hook up
with the Palestinian girl,
who walks around school in a turban?
Oh, sweetie...
the idea of making a
virginal Muslim girl
fall for you doesn't turn you on?
Come on, you woo her, she falls
for you, everybody finds out...
That's it! We cut her down to size,
she can't act all superior anymore.
Not even if I ask you?
Then I'll let you do
whatever you want with me.
But I already do
whatever I want with you.
Not even half of it.
I'm thinking, today would be
a good day to do it. Right?
I call the tow truck, and
they don't come for me.
Well, I don't know.
Here? Right now?
And why not?
But if you're not sure,
let's forget about it.
Hey.
- Samuel, right?
- Yes.
What exactly did you mean to
write here, on my front wall?
T-H-I...
"S."
"This above all: to
thine own self be true."
- Ah.
- It's a quote from Hamlet.
Yes, of course, a quote
from Hamlet. Ingenious.
But...
I think you wanted to write...
Thief, son of a bitch,
or one of those names the
press is calling me lately.
Bring the other two scholarship kids,
and we'll take a photo
of the four of us.
Shaking hands and smiling.
I don't know.
Come, man.
What's wrong with taking a photo?
It could be good for everybody.
For the town, for the
school, even for you.
I wouldn't feel comfortable
doing it, to be honest.
It's OK, kid. I'll report your
brother to the police tomorrow,
see what happens to his parole.
Think about it.
What did he say?
He wants a picture with
the scholarship students.
- Really?
- Yes.
That's why he wanted me to invite
you. His image makeover bullshit.
He doesn't waste an opportunity.
Samuel, don't play
along. You don't have to.
I don't mind doing it.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I don't know. I thought
you were different.
Hello.
Can you come and get me?
Come on, ... we have things to do.
What is this?
Olé.
We have 15 minutes before
they realize I'm not there.
Are you taking your clothes off?
That comes off, too.
But slowly, so I can see you.
Okay. You too. Let's
do it at the same time.
Like this?
Am I doing it right?
Yes, you're doing fucking great.
Hey, cool profile
Yours too. What's up?
Bored. Shall we meet?
Do you have another photo?
I can't believe it.
Explain it to me, please.
You knew it was him who ruined our wall,
and you let him in our home?
- Who?
- The thin one.
But only because he had ulterior
motives, he wanted a picture with him.
What?
Mom, I don't know why you are surprised.
You are the only one dad
still manages to disappoint.
Those people are poison,
Marina, and you know it.
Why are you with them every
time I turn around, Marina? Why?
Why don't you leave them alone?
Because I refuse to let
you get hurt again, Marina!
- Pablo did not mean to hurt me!
- Marina!
It's not the moment. Please.
Then when?
Tell me when is the moment. Why
can't we talk about what happened?
You've spent a fortune on psychologists
to convince me nothing happened.
That life goes on. That
everything would be alright.
And you know what?
Every time you avoid the subject,
I feel like a piece of shit.
I fell in love with
a boy. He infected me.
I need you to say it!
Say it! Say it, Mom!
"My 16-year-old daughter
is HIV-positive."
Do you regret tonight?
It was... intense.
But it was good.
Sure?
Good night.
Good night, gorgeous.
I love you. I love you more than ever.
You! You get a scholarship,
and you thank us like this?
- Guzmán!
- Vandalizing the property of others?
- You disgust me!
- What's going on here?
And who are you? Unbelievable,
the riffraff we get here tonight!
Shall I take that as a
compliment or punch you?
Take it as you will.
- Let's go.
- I won't let this prep boy insult us.
I'm not insulting you,
just stating the facts.
One question.
What do you call people who keep
millions that don't belong to them,
so they can live the way you do?
Thieves, or simply bastards?
You dare come to this house
to insult me and my family.
Who do you think you are, fucking clown?
- What are you doing?
- Okay.
You don't deserve my brother!
Get off me!
Shove your money up your asses!
You! Hey! You are finished!
Tomorrow, everybody at school will
know you are a fucking criminal!
And forget about your scholarship.
Guzmán, please. Are you
okay? Did they hurt you?
Does it hurt a lot?
Polo...
Why don't you go for a walk and
stop making a fool of yourself?
Go!
Guzmán,
don't take it out on
Samuel, he's a good person.
Let's see what the
principal says tomorrow.
Your sister is right.
Samuel is a good person.
Me, not so much.
If you say anything at school,
you'll force me to tell
what I saw in the shower.
Thanks for inviting me.
Nadia.
Nadia, you win.
I spoke in the heat of the moment.
I won't tell on your friend.
Stay a little longer.
Let me show you we
are worth the trouble.
You are too good looking
over your shoulder.
Teach me how to look at you. I
promise I'll be a fast learner.
What's going on, honey?
This one needs to be
taken down a peg or two.
Hey.
Do you plan to remain mute all night?
Had I known, I wouldn't
have stood up for you.
You are clueless, aren't you? Do
you know what I've done for you?
I had it under control, and
you had to come and screw it up.
And now I must clean up after you!
I was protecting you, asshole! It's
what I've been doing my whole life.
I never asked you for that!
Come on, Samu! I won't let those people,
who are a real cancer, laugh at you!
Your whole life you've been blaming
them, maybe you are the cancer.
Is Samuel home?
- Is Samuel here?
- He's sleeping.
He was up all night hugging the toilet.
Says it's hangover.
I think it's the panic of having
to go back to that fucking school.
He can come back, no problem.
That's what I came to tell him.
My brother won't say anything.
Very well.
Was there anything else?
Coffee, water, beer?
Sit down, if you want.
Did you tag my wall?
My letter of introduction.
Next time, finish it.
I liked what you said at the party.
You dared to shout what many
of us think. Or at least I do.
Somebody had to say it.
And, is it true you've been in jail?
You love to ask questions, huh?
Yes, but for a short spell.
Sleeping rough, eating worse.
No women, unless you count
my mother or my lawyer.
A second aunt from Murcia,
I'm not sure why she came
all the way up to see me...
None like you, I can tell you that.
Stay another minute,
and I'll make you iron.
I'm leaving.
Better.
- Bye.
Here you go. Washed and
pressed. By the way...
Fancy girl was here. She
wants you to go back to school.
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org